Santhosh O

- ☑ santhoshomprakash05@gmail.com
- **©** 9360221820
- santhoshomprakash.github.io/portfolio/
- 18/55, Woriyur, Trichy-620003, Tamil Nadu.
- in linkedin.com/in/santhosh-omprakash

Hard Skills

- WordPress
- Micro soft Excel, PowerPoint, word and Access
- HTML
- Canva
- GitHub

Soft Skills

- Observation
- Adaptability
- Communication
- Multi-tasking

Certifications

- Certification of Advance Excel in Coursera
- Certification of Fundamental of digital marketing in Google
- Certification of Business Analytics with Excel in Simple Learn

Education Background

- Lovely Professional University Masters in Business Administration 2022 - Present
- St. Joseph's College
 Bachelor of Commerce General
 2019 2022
- Campion Anglo-Indian School Commerce Completed in 2019

About Me

A Master of Business Administration grad who is enthusiastic and passionate about learning new skills, and acquiring knowledge in the field of marketing, finance and entrepreneurship and additionally has 1 years of experience in digital marketing.

Professional Experience

ANUTAMA ASSOCIATES | Founder - Freelancing

2022 - Present

Service - Audit & Digital Marketing

Key responsibilities:

- Tally Book Keeping
- Goods and Service Tax Registration & Filing
- Social Media Marketing
- MSME Registration
- Website Designing
- Digital Marketing

MD INFOTECH

2021 - 2022

Key responsibilities:

- Website Designing
- Digital Marketing
- Cold calls

Achievements

Santhosh O

- © 9360221820
- santhoshomprakash.github.io/portfolio/
- 18/55, Woriyur, Trichy-620003, Tamil Nadu.
- in linkedin.com/in/santhosh-omprakash

Hard Skills

- Micro soft Excel, PowerPoint, word and Access
- Goods and Service Tax (GST)
- Income Tax
- Ministry of Micro, Small & Medium Enterprises.
- Tally and Book keeping

Soft Skills

- Observation
- Time Management
- Communication
- Multi-tasking

Certifications

- Certification of Tally ERP 9 in St. Joseph's College
- Certification of Advance Excel in Coursera
- Certification of Business Analytics with Excel in Simple Lear

Education Background

- Lovely Professional University
 Masters in Business Administration
 Present
- St. Joseph's College
 Bachelor of Commerce General
 2019 2022
- Campion Anglo-Indian School Commerce
 Completed in 2019

About Me

A Master of Business Administration grad who is enthusiastic and passionate about learning new skills, and acquiring knowledge in the field of marketing, finance and entrepreneurship and additionally has 2 years of experience in Finance.

Professional Experience

ANUTAMA ASSOCIATES | Founder - Freelancing

2022 - Present

Service - Audit & Digital Marketing

Key responsibilities:

- Tally Book Keeping
- Goods and Service Tax Registration & Filing
- Social Media Marketing
- MSME Registration
- Website Designing
- Digital Marketing

SRI RAM ASSOCIATES | Account Assistant

2019 - 2022

Key responsibilities:

- Managed 3 Company's & One Government School & 32 Small- scale Company's.
- GST Filing & Registration.
- Tally Book Keeping.
- Excel works.

Achievements